Guide to the Committee of 100 on the Federal City records [Part I], 1932-2003 MS2017
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Accession 2011.068, 1957-2003; Series 8; 16.5 Linear Feet 11 record cartons
  - WASHINGTON REGIONAL ASSOCIATION OF GRANTMAKERS, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - BOARDSOURCE, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - DC AGENDA, undated; Series 8 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - PIPA ACCOUNTS, Circa 1970 - Circa 1980; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - PIPA ACCOUNTS 2, Circa 1990; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - FINANCIAL STATEMENTS AND TAX RETURNS, 1982, 1994-1998; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - MEMBERSHIP DUES AND LUNCH PAYMENTS, 1993; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - HUMANITIES GRANT, 1987; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - TREASURER'S REPORTS, 1988-1999; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - ACCOUNTANT MEMOS AND LETTERS, 1994-1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - CHILDREN'S ISLAND, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - IRS COMMUNICATIONS, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - FUNDRAISING, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - TRUSTEES MEETING MINUTES, 1994-1999; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - IRS FORM 1099, 1999; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - MEMBERSHIP LIST, 1997; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - INVOICES, 1999; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - BILLS, 1988; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - BILLS, 1997; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - BILLS, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - INVOICES, RECEIPTS, CORRESPONDENCE, 1995; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - MEMORANDA, 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - DEVELOPMENT, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - C100 NEWSLETTER, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - BUDGET - MISC, 1992; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - CHRON FILE, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - GOVERNANCE COMMITTEE, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - DELANO ADDRESS, 1938 March 03; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - MEMBERSHIP DEVELOPMENT, 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - FUNDRAISING - MARPAT APPLICATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - GWU SPECIAL COLLECTION, 1995; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - MEMBERSHIP SURVEY FORM, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - MEMBERSHIP FIELD TRIP, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - MEMBERSHIP ROSTER, 1997; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - MEMBERSHIP DATA AND ROSTER, 1997; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - MEMBERSHIP ROSTER, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - MEMORANDA AND OBITS, 1995-1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - MEMBER BIOS, 1996; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - NOMINATING COMMITTEE, 1994; Series 8 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - MEMBERSHIP APPLICATIONS, 2001; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - OCCASIONAL PAPERS SERIES, 1996; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - OCCASIONAL -- NCPC, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - OCCASIONAL -- RUSK, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - OCCASIONAL PAPER -- PYATT, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - PRESS CLIPPINGS, 1996; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - PRESS CLIPPINGS, 1995; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - PRESS RELEASES, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - PRESS - DEVELOPMENT, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - C100 EXHIBIT GWU LIBRARY, 1995; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - PROMOTIONAL MATERIALS C100 HISTORICAL, 1995-2000; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - SPEAKERS, 1995; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - SPEAKERS, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - SPEAKERS - PAST, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - 75TH ANNIVERSARY CAMPAIGN, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - SUBCOMMITTEE REPORTS, 1996; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - SUBCOMMITTEE SURVEY FORMS, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - TESTIMONY, 1996; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - TRUSTEE BIOS, 1996; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - WASHINGTON DIRECTORY LISTING, 1996; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - TREASURER -- MISC, 1995; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - WEB PAGE, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - BOARD CERTIFICATES, 1996; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - ANNUAL MEETING, 1996; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - SCHWARTZ MEMO ON STADIUM MOU, 1985; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - NCPC -- EDR STADIUM, 1993; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - GIANTS STADIUM MEADOWLANDS, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - C100 POSITION STATEMENT ON STADIUM, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - BINDER OF STADIUM RELATED DOCUMENTS, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - CITY PLAN FOR OLD ANACOSTIA, 1979; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - C100 EXHIBITION, 1995 September; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - TAX RETURN, 1972; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - C100 AMICUS BRIEF, TENLEY AND CLEVELAND PARK EMERGENCY COMTE VS. DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA (, 1988; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - C100 VS. DISTRICT OF COLUMBIA, CASE NO. 88-330, WOODWARD BUILDING, 1987; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - WHAT'S WRONG WITH THE PROPOSED CONVENTION CENTER AT MT VERNON SQ, 1997 September 18; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - C100 STRATEGIC PLAN, 1997-2000; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - TESTIMONY ON WEST ANACOSTIA PARK STADIUM, undated; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - C100 FORUM ON NCPC MONUMENTAL CORE PLAN, 1996 June; Series 8 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - BLAGDEN ALLEY/NAYLOR HISTORIC DISTRICT APPLICATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - ALLIANCE FOR PRESERVATION, 1989; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - DC PRESERVATION LEAGUE, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - ZONING ISSUES, 1988-1989; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - TRANSPORTATION ISSUES, 1987-1989; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - WATER RESOURCES, 1987-1989; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - HISTORIC PRESERVATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - PARKS AND CONSERVATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - PLANNING AND URBAN DESIGN, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - SUBCOMMITTEE ACTIVITIES SUMMARY, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - MEMO ON SUBCOMMITTEES, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - BYLAWS, 1990; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - PROSPECTIVE NEW MEMBERS, 1987-1988; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - C100 HERITAGE REPORT, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - C100 HERITAGE REPORT 2, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - ARTICLES OF INCORPORATION, undated; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - MEMBERSHIP, 1988-1990; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - TRUSTEES LETTERS, 1992; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - SPEAKERS FILE, 1987-1994; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, 1998 August 19; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1989; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1994; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1993; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1992; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1991; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1990; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - APA CONFERENCE EXPENSES, 1992; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - LAPTOP COMPUTER, 1992 March 10; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - PIPA -- AMERICAN UNIVERSITY LAW SCHOOL, 1989; Series 8 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - TRUSTEES MINUTES, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - MEMBERSHIP MINUTES, 1992-1993; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1991-1994; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - MISC CORRESONDENCE AND CLIPPINGS, Circa 1990; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 75TH ANNIVERSARY PLANNING, undated; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - WHITEHURST FREEWAY, undated; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - U.S. ROUTE 240 ROUTING, 1957; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - MT VERNON CONVENTION CENTER, 1997; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - MISCELLENOUS PAPERS, Circa 1990; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - FUNDRAISING, 1999; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - FUNDRAISING -- GENERAL, 1999; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - FUNDRAISING LETTERS OF SUPPORT, 1999; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - DEVELOPMENT -- GENERAL INFO, 1999; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - HELEN SPERRY LEA FOUNDATION, 1999; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - 75TH ANNIVERSARY, undated; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - MARPAT FOUNDATION, 2001; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - ENGLAND FAMILY FOUNDATION, 2000; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - SPERRY LEA CHALLENGE, undated; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - NTHP - DE SCHWEINITZ FUND, 2000; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - PHILIP GRAHAM FUND, 1997; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - ENGLAND FOUNDATION, 1997; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - AC MOORE MD AVE PROJECT, 1999; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - DREYFUS FOUNDATION, 1999; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - DISTRICT CABLEVISION, 1999; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - WHITEHURST FREEWAY, 1989; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - SAMPLES OF TESTIMONY PRESENTED BY THE COMMITTEE OF 100, Circa 1990; Series 8 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - C100 DEVELOPMENT, 1999; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - TRUSTEES MINUTES, 1996; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - DOWNTOWN ACTION PLAN LETTER, 1999; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - TEN GOOD IDEAS FOR DC TRANSPORTATION, 2000; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - INTERMODAL TRANSPORTATION CENTER, 1999; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - 75TH ANNIVERSARY EVENT, 1998 November 18; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - TRUSTEES BIOS, 1999; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - PROPOSED CONVENTION CENTER AT MT VERNON, 1998; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - PROPOSED CONVENTION CENTER AT MT VERNON (CONT'D), 1998; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - PROPOSED CONVENTION CENTER AT MT VERNON (CONT'D), 1998; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - PROPOSED CONVENTION CENTER AT MT VERNON (CONT'D), 1998; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - CONVENTION CENTER HOTEL, undated; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - DC EPA REPEAL HEARING TESTIMONY, 1998 April 12; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - CAFRITZ FOUNDATION GRANT REQUEST, 1999; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - PROPOSED CONVENTION CENTER AT MT VERNON (CONT'D), 1998; Series 8 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - PRISON - WARD 8, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - SHAW HISTORIC DISTRICT, 1996; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - SOLAR BUILDING, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - SQUARE 457, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - SQUARE 483, 1995; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - SQUARE 488, 1997; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - SPECIAL MEETING, 1999 June 15; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - ST PATRICKS, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - WHITE HOUSE PRECINCT TASK FORCE, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - WORLD WAR II MEMORIAL, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - FINANCIAL INFORMATION, 1998; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - PARKS AND CONSERVATION, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - ZONING SUBCOMMITTEE, 1998; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - TRANSPORTATION SUBCOMMITTEE, 1998; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 1998; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - ARENA TASK FORCE, 1995; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - BARNEY CIRCLE, 1997; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - CAMPUS PLANS, 1996; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - CHILDREN'S ISLAND, 1997; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - CONFLICT OF INTEREST, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - COMPREHENSIVE PLAN AMENDMENTS, 1998; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - FRIENDSHIP HEIGHTS SECTOR PLAN, 1997; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - LENFANT PLAN, 1995; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - MCMILLAN RESERVOIR, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - MONUMENTAL CORE FRAMEWORK PLAN, 1996; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - NCRC, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - ELEANOR HOLMES NORTON, 1998; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - PIPA, 1989; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - C100 RETREAT, 1997; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - ROCK CREEK PARK MANAGEMENT PLAN, 1996; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - ROCK CREEK ANTENNAS, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - SQUARE 454, 1996; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - DOWNTOWN HOUSING, 1998; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - TARIFF BUILDING, 1997; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - VICTOR BUILDING, 1997; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - WOODROW WILSON CENTER, 1998; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - DISTRICT BUILDING, 1996; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - WORLD WAR II MEMORIAL, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - WOODWARD AND LOTHROP BUILDING, 1999; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - FUNDRAISING, 2000; Series 8 (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - C100 NOMA TRIANGLE REPORT, 2000 January; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - SMALL AREA PLANS -- NRRC, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - MERIDIAN HILL PARK REQUEST, 2000 March; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - PLANNING TASK FORCE, 1998; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - SOLAR BUILDING PUD CONSENT AGREEMENT, 2000 May 22; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - A VISION FOR DOWNTOWN DC, 1999 November; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - WORLD WAR II MEMORIAL, 2000; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - OFFICIAL STATE HISTORICAL SOCIETY, 1998 May 05; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - YALE LAUNDRY BUILDING, 2000; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - C100 ANNUAL MEETING, 1999 November; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - TRUSTEES MEETING, 2000 May 11; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - FRIENDS OF THE COMMITTEE, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - FINANCIAL REPORTS, 1998; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - TRUSTEES MEETINGS AND MINUTES, 1998; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - MEMBERSHIP MEETINGS AND MINUTES, 1998; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - FINANCE COMMITTEE, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - FINANCE COMMITTEE, 1991 October; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - FINANCE COMMITTEE, undated; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - FINANCIAL, EXPENSES, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - MEMBERSHIP MEETINGS AND MINUTES, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - NEW TRUSTEES BIOS, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - BASEBALL STADIUM, 1997 - 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - BENJAMIN BANNEKER MEMORIAL, 1998 February 27; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - BUZZARD POINT TESTIMONY, 1997 February 7; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - DOWNTOWN CIRCULATOR, 1999 August 26; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - COMP PLAN AMENDMENTS, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - CONFLICT OF INTEREST, 1996; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - CONVENTION CENTER LETTER FROM ATTORNEY, 1998 November 11; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - DEPT OF EMPLOYMENT SERVICES BUILDING, 1998 March 30; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - DOWNTOWN - HERB MILLER, 1997; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - DOWNTOWN HOUSING, 1998; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - INTERMODAL TRANSPORTATION CENTER, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - LENFANT PLAN, 1995; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - MD AVENUE HOUSING PLAN, 1999 June 29; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - MEMORIALS LOCATIONS, 2000; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - NAVY YARD, 1999; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - NY AVENUE, 1996; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - NOMA, 2000; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - WOODWARD AND LOTHROP OPERA HOUSE, 1998; Series 8 (Box 62, Folder 39)